Cheers,
هتافات،
Cheers!
هتافات!
Last time,
آخر مرة،
you left a letter and left.
تركت رسالة وغادرت.
I didn't expect the meeting to be like this again.
لم أكن أتوقع أن يكون الاجتماع على هذا النحو مرة أخرى.
Last time, when I sneaked out of the race,
آخر مرة عندما تسللت من السباق
my brother's men found me
وجدني رجال أخي
and took me back.
وأعادني.
I begged him for a long time,
توسلت إليه لفترة طويلة ،
so he asked me to send you a letter.
لذلك طلب مني أن أرسل لك رسالة.
I'm afraid everyone will worry about me,
أخشى أن يقلق الجميع عليّ ،
so I'm really sorry to leave without saying goodbye.
لذلك أنا آسف حقًا للمغادرة دون أن أقول وداعًا.
Are you Miss Su?
هل انت انسة سو؟
My sister always talks about you,
أختي دائما تتحدث عنك
oh no
أوه لا
This is the flood of water rushing into the Dragon King Temple.
هذا هو تدفق المياه المتدفقة إلى معبد Dragon King.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئ.  لقد كنت مخطئ.
Brother Ming Bao,
الأخ مينغ باو ،
you don't have to blame yourself.
ليس عليك أن تلوم نفسك.
I'm fine now, aren't I?
أنا بخير الآن ، أليس كذلك؟
But can you tell me,
لكن هل يمكنك إخباري ،
who is trying to kill me?
من يحاول قتلي؟
I really don't know.
أنا حقا لا أعرف.
But don't worry,
لكن لا تقلق ،
I've already said it.
لقد قلتها بالفعل.
You, Miss Su,
أنت ، آنسة سو ،
are the one to be covered by my Nether Leopard.
هي التي يجب تغطيتها من قبل Nether Leopard.
I'm sure the world will give me some respect.
أنا متأكد من أن العالم سيمنحني بعض الاحترام.
Thank you, Brother Mingbao.
شكرا لك الأخ مينجباو.
It's not a big deal.
لا مشكلة.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
It's getting late.
الوقت يتأخر.
I'll go back first.
سأعود أولا.
No,
رقم،
keep drinking.
إبقاء الشرب.
I haven't finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد.
Yes, Miss Su.
نعم ، آنسة سو.
It's getting late.
الوقت يتأخر.
You'd better stay here
من الأفضل لك البقاء هنا
and leave tomorrow.
ويغادر غدا.
Let's have a good drink today.
دعونا نتناول مشروبًا جيدًا اليوم.
All right.
حسنا.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Come on,
تعال،
Cheers,
هتافات،
Cheers!
هتافات!
Drink,
يشرب،
Master,
يتقن،
Her Highness was kidnapped by the Nether Leopard of Yifeng Village,
اختطفت صاحبة السمو من قبل النمر السفلى لقرية ييفنغ ،
The Ghost Leopard of Yifeng Village
النمر الشبح في قرية ييفنغ
is the leader of the bandits
هو زعيم قطاع الطرق
on Yifeng Mountain.
على جبل يفينغ.
Yes.
نعم.
So strong.
قوي جدا.
What about the boss?
ماذا عن الرئيس؟
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
all my life, Ming Dabao,
طوال حياتي ، مينج داباو ،
My sister is the one
اختي هي
who worries the most,
من يقلق أكثر ،
Juanjuan,
جوان جوان ،
growing up,
التقدم في العمر،
Because she's fat,
لأنها سمينة
you mean her,
تقصدها
She's not...
هي ليست...
She's not confident,
انها ليست واثقة ،
It's a sin.
انها خطيئة.
I don't know why she's so fat.
لا أعرف لماذا هي سمينة للغاية.
What's wrong with being fat?
ما مشكلة السمنة؟
I told her,
أخبرتها،
"Chubby is fine
"السمين بخير
and suitable to be a thief with me. ",
ومناسب ليكون لصا معي.  "،
He can hold people back,
يمكنه كبح الناس ،
Yes.
نعم.
Oh,
أوه،
it's still useless.
لا يزال عديم الفائدة.
No matter what I say, it's useless.
بغض النظر عما أقول ، فهو عديم الفائدة.
Stop crying.
توقف عن البكاء.
Look how good it is now.
انظروا كم هو جيد الآن.
You're happy again.
أنت سعيد مرة أخرى.
And happy.
و سعيد.
You can eat it again.
يمكنك أكله مرة أخرى.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
This is your credit.
هذا هو رصيدك.
It's all because of you.
كله بسببك.
That's right.
صحيح.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
Exactly
بالضبط
You're my benefactor!
أنت فاعل خير لي!
Great benefactor,
فاعل خير ،
benefactor,
فاعل خير
I don't even know how to thank you.
أنا لا أعرف حتى كيف أشكرك.
You're
أنت على
a second-born parent,
الوالد المولود الثاني ،
Mom,
أم،
No,
رقم،
My mom.
أمي.
It turns out that the Dark Leopard is the Empress'godson, which
اتضح أن النمر المظلم هو الإمبراطورة جودسون ، التي
is a false alarm.
هو إنذار كاذب.
Her Highness shouldn't be in danger.
صاحبة السمو لا ينبغي أن تكون في خطر.
What?
لما؟
Reborn parents?
الآباء المولودون من جديد؟
You call me old.
أنت تدعوني قديم.
Well,
نحن سوف،
Brother,
شقيق،
It can
يمكن
regenerate my brother,
أعيد توليد أخي ،
Right?
حق؟
Little brother,
الأخ الأصغر،
big brother,
الأخ الأكبر،
Brother,
شقيق،
don't cry.
لا تبكي.
Be good,
كن جيد،
Brother is here,
الأخ هنا ،
I'll take care of you.
ساعتني بك.
Come on,
تعال،
Keep doing it,
استمر في فعل ذلك ،
bro. Give me a hug,
أخي.  احضني،
Tell us what's on our mind,
أخبرنا بما يدور في أذهاننا ،
tell us,
أخبرنا،